Copy A College, an new alternative school
at the central of Bangkok.
They say that studying here is the happiest.
Let’s find out why!
School safety with a face-scanning system.
Witn a relaxing atmosphere. Look over there.
We can shoot content as well.
The A/C is freezing here.
As you can see at the back.
For those who love activities,
you must join this room.
Everyone is welcome.
Good-looking labs.
I mean…
high-tech Olympiad labs.
The friendly basketball match
is a must-have every year.
The hype is always a blast.
I'll eat it myself.
Our canteen serves the best food.
Besides food, we're also a whole damn meal.
Do you know why Copy A students are the happiest?
Want to find out? Join Copy A College like us.
(Frame.)
(Lookmo.)
(Est.)
(Wit.)
Can we take the jacket off? It’s too hot.
A cool person doesn’t feel hot.
Um.
If we want others to
see us as alphas, we have to endure it.
Who will look at us?
Hey, get him.
Okay.
-Give me your bag.
-Don't do that.
Give it to me.
Don't do that.
It’s mine.
Let's go.
It's mine, give it to me.
Fuse, take it!
Oh.
Fuse!
Fuse.
Sorry, you good?
Fuse, you okay?
You good?
Uh, what’s going on?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I’m okay.
If anything is bothering you, you can tell us.
Because we’re the Piglets gang.
Since we’re all here, let’s gather.
Come here.
Come on.
Eh?
(The previous day.)
Do you want to know
what makes me feel down?
Yesterday, at Siam,
I found something
that I’ve never known before.
Really?
I knew it.
Why am I never lucky with the lottery like this?
Huh?
Can you tell us again?
Wit!
I'm kidding.
Do you think...
your girlfriend really cheat on you?
But you're with her almost a year now.
A year?
A cheater will always cheat,
no matter how long you've been together.
Have you been cheated before?
Teacher Lookmee told me.
Hey, chill out.
They just walked together.
Maybe they're just friends.
Lookmo, are you even listening?
He told they walked arm in arm.
Friends, my ass.
I figured it out.
What if Jean was about to faint and
that man happened to be a nurse?
So he let Jean link his arm,
and Jean wouldn't fall.
He might be a good person.
Ugh.
Wit.
Get down here.
Come here.
Sit down.
Right here, please.
What are you doing?
Cover his mouth.
What’s been wrong with you since last night?
Act like you're heartbroken.
You girlfriend really cheat on you?
But you're with her almost a year now.
A year? A cheater will always cheat,
no matter how long you've been together.
Hey, Fuse.
Don't feel down.
It's not cool.
If Jean has someone else,
you can also have someone new.
Enough, Frame.
If our friend choose the same path,
it'll end the same way.
But our friend...
should try new things.
What?
Like boys.
Fair skin and red lips like our friend,
he must be a bottom.
Fair skin and red lips, my ass.
You blind?
Get a husband.
Hey,
do you watch way too many BL series?
Which one did you watch?
Can I say it?
Oh no.
Guys, do you have any plans for this evening?
(Mhek.)
My dad asks you to have a meal at my shop.
He won the lottery,
so everything is free today.
That's great.
Come here.
Come on.
Fuse.
Eh?
I'm not tied up.
How's it, kids? Are you full?
We're full.
If I win it again next time,
I'll pay a meal for a whole school.
Yay!
Dad, saves your money.
Hey, it's not a big deal.
No worries.
Thank you.
Keep doing your homework then.
Okay.
Focus on your homework, guys.
I'll help my dad.
Okay.
Fine.
Go ahead.
See you. We'll do our homework.
Ugh.
Frame, look at these timid boys.
They're even wearing uniforms at Siam.
Have you ever got a smack by sneakers?
Hey, hey.
Fuse, was it this person?
What?
Who?
Yeah, it's this person.
Oh, he's good-looking.
Huh? What did you say?
Wit.
Listen, why did you praise others?
Our friend is the most handsome.
My Mommy tells me not to lie.
But he's really handsome though.
I told you.
His aura is so alpha.
Look at our friend.
So grubby.
Wait, wait.
Our friend can be an alpha too.
He just needs someone to train him.
Hey.
Who's gonna train him?
It's obviously me.
Take me as an example.
Enough, You're not an alpha, just a player.
Est, I'm your boss.
(Nai.) (Copter.) (Champ.)
(Tee.)
Damn, I know who will be a coach for Fuse.
Who?
Tee.
Right, Fuse.
Do you know him?
I've seen him say hi to you.
They knew each other.
I saw you two hanging out in junior high school.
In junior high school,
Fuse once didn’t finish his homework.
And Tee finished it all for him.
What a hard carry.
Whoa.
So...
he can train him, right?
But I think he’s way too nerdy.
Excuse me.
Would you mind not taking photos?
Damn.
He killed it.
I think he's not a nerd.
Do you know a hot nerd?
A person who pretends to be a nerd.
But I think he's full of rizz.
I think...
Whoever his partner is
has to handle how rough he is.
Rough? How?
Like commanding the partner to do dishes?
Wit!
Why?
What's it then?
I guess whoever his partner is,
he wouldn't just take his partner to have a meal,
watch a movie,
or wait for his partner
to get acne treatment, as our friend does.
Fuse, is that all you did?
What do you expect me to do?
No wonder why she's leaving from you.
Okay, Fuse. I got you a tip.
What's it?
Take your phone out.
What?
Type what I said.
Okay, got it.
C
O
P
Y
Six.
Nine.
You can search it now.
Okay.
Shit, Frame! What did you show me?
Hey, what's that sound?
You?
Or you?
It's him.
Where are you going?
Let me go.
Or you?
Dad, customers.
Good job.
Whatever.
Hey, mine is as huge as my dad's.
Sorry.
I didn't mean to drag you out here.
Will you go back?
I guess I can't.
Sorry.
I'll buy you snacks.
Never mind.
Right.
It's late now and good kid don't go home late.
So I’d better go. Bye.
Shit.
I forgot my bag.
Mine is also at the shop.
I’ll take care of it.
Wit.
Tee and I forgot our bags.
Huh?
Can you bring them to the bus stop?
Huh? What did you say?
Hey.
How did it go?
Uh.
My phone is dead.
Will you be able to get into your house today?
The key is inside my bag.
And no one is home.
How about sleep over at my house?
Can you get into your house?
Can I sleep over?
Of course.
You’re always welcome at my home.
Great.
Let’s go.
Come on.
You’re so slow.
Come here.
Ugh.
Are you teasing me?
Come here.
Come here
Can you wear it?
Yeah.
It’s so big.
Thanks.
Good thing tomorrow is Saturday.
If not, I have to wash my uniform.
You can wear mine.
I can even lend you my underwear.
Hey, you don’t have to.
I’d rather freeballs and go to school.
Twenty plus twenty plus twenty plus seven.
Oh, that's easy. The answer is six-seven.
What did you watch earlier at the shop?
Frame showed me a porn.
I couldn't turn it off in time. So I'm screwed.
Watching it at the shop?
I didn’t even watch it and thing happened.
Shall we watch it now?
Sure.
Does Frame…
watch it like this?
Frame is open.
He’s fine with men, women,
human, animals, or things.
What about you?
Women, for sure.
Tee.
Hmm?
Can I ask you something?
Have you ever kissed someone like this?
Huh?
Someone like you has never done it?
Oh.
So you can’t train me anymore.
Train what?
Well…
Shall we try?
Try what?
Like this.
Like this?
No, no, no.
I mean, just kissing.
I just want to know how to do it.
Then close your eyes.
Wanna do it?
Let's do it.
I’m sorry.
It’s fine.
Shall we try again?
Um.
Then hold my waist.
-Sorry.
Why did you say sorry?
What about you?
I’m sorry for…
asking you to watch it
and…
I’m sorry for…
asking you to…
I’m also sorry
that I did…
Shall we continue?
You okay with it?
Are you okay?
Um.
That’s enough.
I’m sorry.
It’s fine.
I’m the one who started this.
How about praying now?
Are you mad at me?
I just don’t want you taking it lightly.
What do you mean?
Don’t ask anyone to try this again.
Okay?
Because I had to
hold myself back so much last night.
What?
Fuse, are you free today?
Why?
Let's watch a movie.
That movie is in theaters now.
Nah.
Why?
You really want to watch it, don’t you?
Right.
It’s available only a few theaters.
Really?
Um. How about we catch a movie...
around 1 PM?
Alright, you can book the tickets.
Okay, I’ll send them to you after I've booked.
Tee.
Can I borrow your clothes?
(Book.)
What do you think about...
the class rep who gave the wrong due date,
so the entire class got an incomplete grade?
What should we do with him?
I already apologized.
Apologized?
But we still have to be here.
How will you take responsibility for this,
class rep?
Hey, I’m joking.
Take it easy.
Everyone makes mistakes.
You’re the same as Wit.
Look.
He’s hard of hearing.
What?
Hey.
Don’t you dare talk bad about the class rep,
or you’ll get in trouble.
How’s it? I’m cool, right?
What was that loud noise, everyone?
Can you be peaceful for just one day, please?
(Teacher Lookmee.) For a class rep, follow me.
You’re dead.
Wit, are you afraid?
You should be afraid of
not having your work to submit. Get it done.
Hurry get it done, Wit.
Hey, isn’t Fuse coming?
What are you smiling at?
Nothing.
We haven’t met each other lately.
Are you busy?
Look.
I’ve just finished this one.
The male lead is an ice hockey player.
So cool.
Why don’t you play some sports?
Nah.
I’m lazy.
Hey, why?
You haven’t tried it yet.
I'll be right back.
I just saw a famous donut shop that just opened.
Shall we go?
This bouquet doesn’t suit you.
Yes!
You told me to be an athlete
but I’m not into it,
so you told me that’s boring.
Why don’t you find an
athlete boyfriend in the first place?
Yeah!
If you don’t like me, then just say it.
Don’t tell me to be somebody else.
Stop lying to me.
I don’t want to be a fool anymore.
When did you come here?
I didn’t see you at all.
I joined the movie halfway through.
I have a tutoring class at 3 PM.
So I just find something to do.
Whoa.
That’s crazy.
Thank you, anyway.
Actually,
if you have any problems, just hit me up.
Oh.
It’s already 3 PM.
Aren’t you going to class?
Um.
I gotta go.
Tee.
When will your class finish?
I’ll wait and go home with you.
Then let’s meet here.
Okay.
Hello.
Hello, hello?
-Where are you? -Can you hear me?
I’m at home.
Hello, can you hear me?
Hey!
I’ll tell Mom if you lie.
Right.
I’m not lying now.
I’m outside. What do you need?
Did you see a package in front of
our house this morning?
What package?
I didn’t see it.
How come?
The status showed it was delivered since yesterday.
Or…
did you not go home last night?
I did but…
Uh…
Whatever.
You have to rush home and check the package.
Or I’ll tell Mom you didn’t go home.
Fuse, why don’t you eat something at my shop?
I have to rush home, sorry.
Fuse?
Tee.
Do you have any plans after this?
Let's go grab some food.
I’ve already had a plan.
Bye.
I know. I’m going home now.
Will my package be stolen?
It won’t.
I’m gonna call a cab. I’ll hang up.
(Real time pics, bro.)
With mom, my ass.
It's more like a man.
(Where are you?)
(I’m leaving first.)
Are you already leaving?
Um.
I thought we were gonna go together.
My sister want me to rush home so I’m leaving first.
You should at least tell me.
It’s just going home together.
Don’t make it a big deal.
I gotta go.
It’s just going home together.
Don’t make it a big deal.
Why does this always happen to me?
Tee.
Seriously, are you upset with me?
I'm upset.
On that day,
I went there to see you,
but you stood me up like that.
How could I not be upset?
Shall we try again?
I want to know that I...